I welcome back to the home retreat
Haislip a lady retreat DeRose I call it
online retreat sometimes I call it at
home retreat at home a trade sounds more
friendly way when you put your address
online community retreat Daruma rotate
Daruma dr. garlicky remark on and the
picture we have here is somebody
shooting in error come barakatuh me lick
etcd addresses or on my name the name of
today's class is called arrows and
factories don mcallister e in E
disappered Dada Dada public and I want
to teach you an important Tibetan word
before we start so I get my Nigeria
under suave young patina that depends go
look at online Jacqueline Jake
Thank You Lane that means to shoot an
arrow or to throw a spear pen pratima
name back Bona a tamil m / tompa and
oftentimes in books about karma you hear
about a thing Stanley knows about it
called a servant a little on Phuket and
karma and abandon art and tongue Holly
to stand it out and - Holly - that you
do now which is going to throw your next
life it's going to decide what is your
next life that any idolic are my idol
aku Kazakh Ron young akan Valley Parkway
- Podrick Utada idiot on bamboo Toscana
pocket open pretty good anda so like if
you're a very good person in this life
JD chica and the orang yang sangat bike
timer which will shoot you into the
future life as a human again and a con
man what Carmen akan Berlin / anda
capacitor but he took Sobotka - yeah
lucky and then usually they say there's
two Carmen's called Pangea kill a which
is the throwing camera Denby ah Sonya by
common Otacon added to occur by
indiscipline fakie which means finishing
hammer dead Cambodia at a chalk shaky
layer practical they always in the
ancient books - a master painter and his
student painters
Tanaka Solomon banning Canada um pouco
kunana master palooka Stanberry Lucas
so the master Paynter will take in the
old days they will take a piece of
charcoal and there was sketched like if
you're painting a person they will
schedule the person today's a master
palooka CMOS Alalu a conman gamble
zapato aaron tenbroek a conman Watts
casa seperti chica Adama Lucas's Oren
break occurred when gum bars get Susumu
aura
so that's called that's like throwing
common like it decided you will be a
human being
daddy do support a caramel M / - mama
Tuscon undetermined jetty panacea but
what's the details of your new life
Tapia perigean kite open bar Wanda will
you be rich will you be poor Papa will
you be sure piccata thinking I can you
be a woman will you be a man I got my
daddy's heart I wanted that matter for
the student painters that the master
says paint this part blue paint this
part yellow paint this part green a
little metaphor a paramour EP Lucas
massaman attack attack partying anything
and Peru pertain in heating and cooling
but can anything on he chow and in
Tibetan s called so PA de bas a
deception color which fills in the
details of your life which is thrown by
destroying Chi Minh City it - karma
young monkey see region he took and yog
dealer Parker on a karma Mille ampere
now the reason I mentioned those two is
I think I've discussed them before in
the lemon in this lemon series Saqqara
Allison say I mean II put can't do any a
de la Cite pickle size with a mubarak
esprit de la creme de la merced ela but
so far this series took ten years okay
that be said Joe
Eenie said you need to love the
challenge to be honest I don't remember
what I taught you I didn't teach you the
truth yes I think that a peroxide but I
thought that is this is not destroying
karma that I taught you before the
papaya in psychotic and Harini Adela in
E pecan caramel empyrion say a gherkin
say Bologna
before the throwing karma and the
details karma were called Pangea Kili
and sob tequila sebelum na karma melon
patent karma INSEAD I suppose
particulate chalk shakily yeah and now
we have a slightly different word which
is pen jackal a and do particular
Saqqara keep them Amelie case a ticket
kappa bert beta young a dollop in check
you lay than to check you lay the first
kind of karma is is the same you can
think of a spear or an arrow can watch
any sport ama at rosamma and abba-zaba
maker can tumble at opana
but the duplicate layer I don't want you
to think of student painters tapia to
jakeel a saya tidak in an American Moret
palookas I want you to think of a
factory saya Union and Mo make your
cancer but they do a lot of things and
then a car comes out of the factory
Camila cocaine by knockout and
commodious super mobile quarterly popery
okay let's read the text and then you'll
be more comfortable parakeet a Mumbai
attacks that comedian and a Carla p.m.
on the dot and I am not uniquely your
lap almost sooner so you really have to
get familiar with these twelve links of
dependent on a banana Harris Vanzetti a
crap turn and do a blast out and Qatar
can't do man muscle means you should be
able if I say what's link number 3
Wesley number five you should be able to
say immediately what their Brad Jessica
same an attack on a patent number tikka
a patent and kuru say I'm a
neurochemical five euros yeppity-do
taquile some Burnham's Shiva miso soup
arepa
sorry nah nah per kg cooperate but the
bats are kept a super Cooper number two
per sip - chip Akira juni but dashi
you know we had to say guitars mengapa
can you say what son Bharata young - it
is I heard of Kali and I can do you know
all the traveling like individual
friends
Sakura Stella and a thousand more to a
blast out that supported the money
defeat o or individual and who is a
defeatist banana in luck sure do look
sugar you should be familiar with how
these are grouped into groups under
Harris a crab leg and Sarah
riccati Brotman jetty Colombo and there
are forklifts data but color if you're
studying the Tibetan and you're
following the Tibetan chick saccharine
chica and a pleasure paucity pet that
anime cootie bus
I want to say unfortunately sir I get
magnetic and sighing yeah the word in
Tibetan yin lock in the word in Sanskrit
anger cutter deposit opinion locked on
capitalist kurta anger anger they are
the same word for the links and the same
word for the groups
Rekha Adela Katayama in 2010 Katayama
auto Colombo
so I'm gonna use different teddy Sayaka
propraetor super detail group sort of
links
Adam Park Lompoc Dalton first one is
called Peggy Ella important body support
NJ aquí en la that's the shooting group
it took group member
second is tequila Couture other
character hito Atala cribbage a billion
lag means what was shot
like you can say the arrow prati up int
tempeh under visa
pilla Panna so Group one is kind of like
the archer clocks at Udacity Pomona and
group 3 is kind of like the arrow then
Colombo katika are a supportive partner
who is like the factory crooked to us
support a public good for a number to be
debian like they it's kind of like what
the factory puts out group impart a tell
us about the app I am Patrick Clark on
so there are four groups daddy adam but
gwampa arrow shooter
Bhuvana car producing factory products
eMobile the arrow which you shoot anayia
anapana and the car which comes out of
the factory then Moe billion kilowatt
array public
okay they are my reppin is seven double
the purple top with don't take on a
llama do chicolini sobbing table with
them now if we're going to talk about it
in terms of gardening
sekarang takaku takaku bachata tom
hollie totally still a burqa boon then
the first thing like a harness turning
Kassala Bahaman it's like the gardener
who plants puts the seed in the ground
idle as a party to conquer pool yeah I'm
gonna but can be Betty Donna and the
actions you take because you have
misunderstanding dancing ducking young
under anvil karana and Emma Milliken
xalapa Hammond like the seed that's
planted by the kernel developer TPP
young Lee tandem or I took and kaput
okay now the earth where you put the
seed
sekarang Donna and Amanda but can be bit
it's the first half of link number 3
which is awareness adolescent Gary
Talton America young italica cetera
so when you when you say to your husband
I'm not stupid you're stupid which is
link number 2
today katakana ricotta kepada Swami
sided upper to under because you thought
whoever isn't gonna end up repeated but
the dearest nearsighted a broken Ababa
Seminary me cycle on small once I come
on in what's link number 3 mind of the
wife in the kitchen at the time that she
says I'm not stupid you're stupid
and she hears her own words and those
words are imprinted on her mind any
other a picker and III Teterboro
porosity a mangaka sadita puto and
Oberto
Tandy Amanda narcotic upon yes dearie 10
kata-kata a to togetic typical Anya
we call that link number 3 keep them in
your putti Inomata come and pick it out
under at the moment of planting
Bekir ananda sad banana man now the
second half of link number 3 is going to
be sakura tange about Jenka to atari
Titano motika the mind after the seed as
the seed opens and goes into the manhood
a gunman JTP Kira's wok to be Peter
Phuket and Masuka Raheem EBU
so let's consider these links number one
which is misunderstanding your husband
said America topic teaming consultant in
a number Sato Holika Xalapa hamantash a
link number 2 which is doing some karma
Thank You magenta number 2 a young la
Cucaracha show in the first half of
consciousness turn camera and keep that
up at my masuka's Tanaka said Aaron Burr
Tama those two and a half swings it's
okay that don't zoom in Tibetan it
means if you added another half you
would get three you see so that's the
Tibetan way to say two and a half Jade
and Tsubasa Tibet Manabe casting about
yin to Panipat antica talent appeared a
confidence thing uh so what was knocked
out I I do I think it's a blue cloud
around the shooting links Samrat I can
convert is Anita Simon gambar security
to our bureau circuit artists out on my
name
now we'll go back to the Turks segurança
pack and compile it attacks Sabine
Lisicki gamba now you take that seed
saben Saqqara a little solid shoe which
is water marina chu-young is fertilizer
young fer Shur means you'd make it kind
of wet and warm
Thank You Morgan sure sure Pratibha and
ammonia acaba is an ancient word that
means what a mom does to their kid when
they feed them and they take care of
them so camera means these extra things
water fertilizer sunlight they are
supporting the state they are feeding
the same young buck at acuña and crafty
Soren Ebola koukin but a necrotic
American Brima kundan Rawat Marika
seperti Hal Houston bad IRA poop poop
cinema tahi and the fertilizer and the
Sun line you know it's eight and nine
thirty thousand young man is a party I
attend poop-poop
conceded Mata Hari and a Tau a needle
upon dance Sibylla
they make the comic seat ready to give a
baby
trecorum what beep it karmis yeah Mikasa
can't buy in terms of the death process
tell em how process come at the end we
can speak more specifically of the one
seed which is going to be activated to
shoot you next life kita the puppies are
allah be specific teresa to Papeete yeah
i canti at this gun on top man named
buck Cooper under pre Cunha
and we talked about being very careful
to make the hospital room comfortable
and speak quietly and remind people of
their good deeds done bachata
sanguinetti sangapur hottie hottie took
number two on kumis Akiyama temporary
charity mt.abu double Nootka orin orin /
Burton pike Marika
so you can explain link 8 and Link 9 in
general terms of your whole life you
should do coffee meditation or you
should regret the bad things in 10:30
and abuse and Mandela's competent
abundant out ensemble and alum ha boom
boom de richelieu he to Panda and
arsenic on copy editor Seattle and
rehearse - a little helper oh yeah under
lakukan
or you can think of eight and nine more
specifically as the last moment of your
general awareness of this lifetime
before your mind shifted like an animal
and a department maker can tell
abandoned mill ancestral pakusa
Swatantra here Kassadin Amanda's
overheat opini sebelum pucara and a
precursor cap akhirin Young's a
particular I say last moment of your
life your general awareness of this
world shifts to animal state of mind I
don't mean you become an animal you have
an animus man I don't mean katika Simon
got the confidence attracted hit upon de
casa de uma Andres to Nia in e para que
circuit card and Peter and hey one Tita
party under majority hey one Dan under
milky tokoha one saya Tita promise Oh
poquito I mean your mind dies
massotherapy Kiera and Amati
ninety-nine percent a year in mind dice
symbol and below Sybilla percent P Kira
and Amati
and all this left is we call nuke some
nukes him dancing oil does he suck you
time when you put yeah yep like primeval
mind the mind which you've had for
billions of lifetimes it is Bharati
support typical and papa padronia
on Dominica's llama million to hit upon
by the way that's why it's very
difficult to remember what happened in
your past life among it was a populist
and a Sulha don't opening an apparent
the jetty decreed by Massillon 99% of
your mind
died during that last minute of
awareness and a departmental assembly
assembly represent a typical and a
nominee girl Slama money tracker kisara
so that seed in the garden gets its
water and it's fertilizer saying a PPT
Taman when Deepika and I are tanpopo
yeah by LinkedIn it's the feet the seat
gets very far
so somebody thought on Sapolu beep it
menjadi lefty did she make a way from
bolognese cheaper and it makes it
certain that that seed is going to throw
a new life tentative ammonia pasty
PowerPivot Ekambaram Park and create
open Peru
so therefore link eight nine and ten I
can I do about and lapels and be like I
like to call them factory links so
company put yeah thousand popping they
are producing your new body and your new
mind America proxy to Papa and I can
pick it and borrow and I linked ten that
new bar in mind are almost ready for
shipping
so somebody taught and subpool to put
and picker and borrow hampers yet open
Irie man
so again I showed an image here of link
eight nine and ten and by the way the
links are equal to the old clocks in
like one two three four five so eight
nine and 10 are gonna be where eight
nine and ten o'clock that is scary lucky
Seminole chicken competition eat at it
out on telephones be London super Omaha
mom Talton Tata any salmon and jam llama
Zapatista to to Ithaca Pat Lima DET e
lappen som be London's Apollo I can't
brother dictum but buckle Telepan sambal
intense a pool
dorita so we finished the shooting links
dedicated manila second thousand my name
is finish the factory which is getting
your new body and mine ready then get
down near a second public young member
to put and togetherness yep now let's go
back to the text
psychotic attack America begin your
question
Jesse turning some Germany so let's go
to the moment that the seat splits open
and the spell comes out JD barakatuh ma
su casa at P Peter Phuket and Tunis
keluar this is like the production that
comes out of the factory in is a party
products E and Kahlua Terry public and
that's linked number eleven
rebirth yeah I die like a lion cabal
yeah it's gonna be another production
link will come to it later
Adela get out and row to see the Paquita
a con man Bastian on T so if the factory
is the seed already wet and fertilized
Jacob ricotta people yang sudah pasa
dandy boy
then the production coming out of the
factory the first part of that
production is your rebirth
mother products Iqaluit re papi buggin
Tama dari prophecy - I see link number
11 and I've added 12 done tell em comedy
CDI doubly hard outer numbers the blood
and snot embark on probably because
that's going to be another production
but it's gonna in the text it's coming a
little bit later
goodnight to akan menjadi sapporo to see
light capital M taxi to young a cantata
Cambodian Vonda Shepard target chain to
Tinashe timings so cheering Pat under
catch a solvent a tender chetana
knee Papa Dipper so what's the arrow
that gets shot
Teddy bon appetit timba who's the
shooter do you remember chef up a Nimba
yeah I misunderstood my husband
Camus Tensei but a sorry sorry number
three in my mind is where where the seed
is planted estimate re Tottenham at Zika
pick rasayana arrow that gets shot the
current Panna up I hear catalysis is
second half of thirdly thing up again
cut to a thousand to design the mine and
Kingdom
Kieran young master the two guys in the
boat your mind and your body inside your
mother's womb Cambodian tour on the
prowl pick your intent to poo and adi
talam rahim yonder and then your sense
organs organ interval the contact of
your mind with the outside world because
of those organs contact to get out and
out and undo Niall organ or cut or cut
it to and in the feelings you have about
that contact ID that's think that's the
stinger that food smells good
gentle and Prasad yeah under me leaky
tent incognito McConnell pupusas
mechanical baby I like that smell all
right though like this yes yes
carbo it to death of the links chimp are
setting up out order arrow which is
thrown a de lapin ah hyung deal
important we call in Tibet they're
called result links which are from
talent positive apricot ISA put hisself
out annyeong Dylan Parkin
okay one more small piece here okay so
now let's talk about link number 12 scar
America tappet era tan tantowel number
12 hours to properly dollar what's the
technical name sir Panama technician
yeah
come on the Mook in 2001 sorry
that's with maybe is it no Marty and
Eggman c'mon Keenan Benoit
my bank so now we're talking about death
and maybe aging in it out on comity and
on moonkin penguin
that's another Fred that we took we
promise you one more production link
right the car that came out of the
factory it is a path onto the sea lion
guitar attendees are two lucky Tonto to
second experiences of killing all the
time man man jetty towards saqqara is a
car which is produced in the factory of
length 8 9 and 10 which is the fantasy
adela mobile young the product city
public about and elephants Balanta
Sapolu young group a most boring class i
gave you in this group I think so it
took class Impala members and con young
saya pre-cut under detail and say can
you teach something that we can really
use unique a toccata man Thomas a
magnification epidemic on circuses were
too young did that would happen at the
particular and I apologize that I don't
always show you how to use it as a
lalomanu you can Tara Munna Kenya
there's not one word of dharma that you
cannot Maya undersea datapath kanakam
and the older you get the more you
appreciate all the things that people
have taught you which I have many smack
into WA and asking the peepee salmon
carcass mahalia aura or ontological
young saya because in these last two
days of classes to re-track yeah we
talked about the sections of the wheel
of life that kind of hang together
Peter tank became another he taught that
he to pamper kyun-jung support deeper
sama
we are now in a position to answer
an important question yes Karan where
the detail imposes you to Punjab panting
how many lives are going up under
created by yang terjadi tell us a - rota
okay and if you want to know that gamble
allowed access 11 plus Thank You Stanley
for translating so happily mikasa
Stanley undocumented samarkand an
advocate of Archaea
you